■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
《24 小时》 前期提要
这件事不用再争了  乔
We're done debating this, joe.
本杰明·朱玛屠杀了20多万百姓
The un's been issuing reprimands and economic sanctions
联合国已经进行了经济制裁
While benjamin juma has slaughtered over 200,000 of his own people.
如果我们不阻止还会继续恶化
That number will continue to grow if we don't stop him now.
有什么发现吗
Did you find something?
是的  还不能确定你儿子怎么死的
I did. it doesn't confirm how your son died,
不过很可疑
but it is suspicious.
接着说
I'm listening.
他的女朋友萨曼莎
His girlfriend, samantha,
在罗杰自杀三天后收到一大笔钱
Received a large lump sum deposit about three days after roger's suicide.
你是说自杀是假象
You mean his alleged suicide.
我会亲自和她谈的
I'll talk to her myself.
抱歉要打断一下  参议员
Sorry for interrupting, senator.
我们有张杰克·鲍尔的传票
We have a subpoena for jack bauer.
他正接受美国参议院的审讯
He's being questioned by the united states senate.
我们需要鲍尔先生  马上要
We need mr. bauer immediately.
CIP防火墙保护本国所有的基础系统
The CIP firewall protects every infrastructure system in this country.
如果被攻破  系统就会被攻击
If it were breached they would all be vulnerable.
司法部要告我违法
The department of justice is about to file criminal charges against me.
我恐怕没法帮你
I'm not exactly in a position to help you.
这次事件的背后  有你的熟人
One of the men behind this threat is someone you know.
你认为托尼用袭击祖国以求公正吗
You think tony's looking for justice by attacking this country?
帮我找到阿尔梅达  你自己问他啊
Help me find almeida, and you can ask him yourself.
托尼·阿尔梅达在哪里
Where's tony almeida?
我不告诉你
I'm not talking to you.
你来决定吧
This is your call.
随你怎么做
Do whatever it takes.
好吧  好吧  好吧
All right! all right! all right!
我告诉你我知道的
I'll tell you what I know!
上一次我见到阿尔梅达
Last time I saw almeida...
没你和联调局的事
There's nothing you or the fbi can do about this.
别管闲事
Just stay away.
托尼  说话啊
Tony, just talk to me.
托尼
Tony!
GSA117  这里是东北三号
Gsa 117, this is northeast three.
请讲  航管局
Go ahead, air traffic control.
建议高度7000英尺
Advise passing 7,000.
降到那里应该会平稳一些
Should be a smoother ride for you down there.
收到  东北三号
Roger that, northeast three.
GSA 117  输入下降1500英尺指令
Gsa 117, enter descent for 1,500.
我与GSA117失去联络
I've lost comm with gsa 117.
给联调局打电话
Call back fbi.
告诉他们有架767失去控制
Tell them we have a 767 on approach no longer under our control.
以下事件发生在上午九点至十点
有人和GSA117联系上了吗
Anybody get through to global skies 117 yet?
还没有  长官  我们正在努力
Not yet, sir. we're trying everything.
飞机到哪儿了
Where's the plane?
肯尼迪机场东南120英里处
120 miles miles southwest of jfk.
在这里
Right here.
好吧  我们必须要提醒他们
All right, we have to alert them somehow.
分析下飞行路线
Analyze the projected flight path.
看一下有没有可能
Figure out if there's any way we can
通过地面标识联系他们
Contact them visually from the ground.
托德  查下乘客记录
Todd, access the passenger records.
-尽可能找些手机号进行联系    -是  长官
Get as many cell numbers as you can and try calling them. yes, sir.
紧急频道呢
Nothing on the emergency channels?
他们并没和任何人联系
They're not trying to contact anyone,
不过刚下降了1500英尺
but they just descended to 1,500.
不知道是谁下的指令
I don't know on whose directions.
长官  我好像找到了
Sir, I think I've got it.
-找到什么了    -您听
Got what? listen to this.
这是我们失去联络之后录的
This was recorded right after we lost comm with them.
GSA117  这里是东北三号
Gsa 117, this is northeast three.
请讲  航管局
Go ahead, air traffic control.
建议高度7000英尺
Advise passing 7,000.
保持1500英尺
Maintain 1,500.
前方预报有小股气流
Traffic ahead reporting minor turbulence.
降到那里应该会平稳一些
Should be a smoother ride for you down there.
他们以为是我们发布的指令
They think they're communicating with us.
这里是调查局
Bureau.
我是航管局  东北三号
This is air traffic control, northeast three.
我找莫斯探员  有紧急情况
I need to talk to agent moss. it's urgent.
我给你接过去
I'll put you through.
莫斯探员  还是航管局的电话
Agent moss, I'm transferring air traffic control again.
情况怎么样  西德
What's your status, sid?
攻破防火墙的那帮人
The people that broke through the
控制了我们的一架飞机
Firewall are controlling one of my planes.
他们冒充航管局指挥飞行员
They're talking directly to the pilot as if they're air traffic control.
只要飞行员不知道他是冒充的
As long as the pilot thinks he's talking to one of us,
就会一直听他们指挥
He'll do whatever they tell him.
天啊
My god...
GSA117  这里是东北三号
Gsa 117, this is northeast three control..
请讲   航管局
Go ahead, air traffic control.
准备执行新的飞行路线
Standby for new runway assignment.
右转  飞行坐标060
Turn right, heading zero-six-zero.
调整雷达向量至跑道31左侧
Intercept radar vectors for runway three-one-left.
东北三号  我们这里显示
Northeast three,
肯尼迪机场并无天气变化
we're showing jfk weather systems unchanged.
没错  我们更改了风向指标
Yeah, we've had a change in wind direction.
本地确实有风向剪力的风险
Locally, there's danger of wind shear.
收到  东北三号
Roger that, northeast three.
转至坐标060
We're turning to heading zero-six-zero now.
好了  路线改了
All right, they're changing course.
我刚跟航管局的西德·保罗森
I just got off the phone with sid
通完电话
Paulson at northeast three air traffic control.
阿尔梅达那伙人确实侵入系统了 拉里
Almeida's group is definitely in their system. larry...
安全局刚刚发现了
Nsa just detected it.
他们正布置入口标识  但并不乐观
They're trying to locate the point of entry, but they're not optimistic.
先别管他们怎么入侵的系统
Forget where they got into the system.
怎么才能把他们弄走
How the hell do we get them out?
不知道  以前从没发生过
they don't know. They've never seen anything like this before.
我守住这边
I got the alley.
拉里  换到2频道
Larry, go to channel two.
好了  请讲
Yeah, go ahead.
希望你查到schector的消息了
I hope you got information from schector.
这事闹大了
This thing has escalated.
闹大了  什么意思
"escalated" how?
阿尔梅达挑了一架767飞机
Almeida's group has picked out a 767 in flight.
现在已经控制了飞机
They're controlling it.
什么  为什么  要飞到哪儿
What? why, to what end?
不知道  不过必须要找到他
I don't know, but we've got to find this guy.
谢克特怎么说
What did schector say?
被杀之前没说什么
Not much before he was killed.
什么
What?
我们立刻封锁了大楼  他就在那儿
We sealed off the building immediately; we know he's in there.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事  干的太干净了
Yeah, it was surgical.
我派特警队去搜查大楼
I'm sending you swat teams to search the building.
谢谢
Thank you.
特警队已经出发了
Swat teams are on their way.
我觉得你有麻烦了
I think you got a problem.
谢克特死了才几秒钟
Almeida called that office seconds
阿尔梅达就打电话到办公室
after schector was killed.
他怎么会知道我在那里的
How do you think he knew I was there?
我想他被监视了吧
I'm assuming he had him under watch.
我认为是你办公室的问题
I think it came from your office.
-什么    -联调局内部人泄的密
What? someone from inside the fbi had to tip him off.
只有他们知道我和你一起来的
They were the only people who knew I was going with you.
不  我不相信
No, I can't believe that.
我也不想相信托尼是恐怖分子
Yeah, and I didn't want to believe tony almeida was a terrorist,
不过我们都要面对事实
But at some point we have to deal with the facts,
我们不想相信的  是事实
Not what we want to believe is true. look, jack, I read your file.
杰克  我看过你的档案
look, jack, I read your file.
我知道你有多疑的倾向
I know you have a propensity for not trusting people,
不过  我的人一直在很努力的
But my team has been working around the
找出阿尔梅达  他们是好样的
Clock to find almeida; they are all good agents.
房顶上的狙击手怎么回事  说啊
Explain to me how they got a sniper on the roof that quickly.
我告诉你  阿尔梅达监视了谢克特
I told you, almeida had schector staked out.
我们在谢克特的办公室才10分钟
We were in schector's office for ten minutes.
他们没法在这么短的时间内派狙击手来
There is no way they got a shooter in position that fast.
从现在起  除非你知道哪里出了问题
Now, until you know where the leak is,
不然你就得假定有内鬼
You have to assume that you've got a bad agent,
并且做好防范措施
And you need to work around him.
杰克  我让你来是帮助处理谢克特的事情
No offense, jack, but I brought you here to help with schector,
而不是来指手划脚的
Not to co-manage this operation.
你带我来是为了帮你找出阿尔梅达
You brought me here to help you find almeida.
我要再强调一下你得小心内鬼
And I am warning you, you better be careful who you let in.
鲍尔先生  请把枪交出来
Mr. bauer, I need you to surrender the gun.
基尔纳探员
Agent kilner...
在我回来之前把杰克·鲍尔关到你车里
Jack bauer, put him in your vehicle till I get back.
好的
Yes, ma'am.
这边请
This way, sir.
情况如何
What's your status?
我们把这包围了  一只鸟也飞不出去
We secured the building; all exits are covered.
等特警组一过来
When swat team gets here,
在卫星侦测的帮助下  我们就一间间屋子的搜
We'll have video feed and we'll sweep the building room by room.
如果狙击手还在这  他铁定跑不掉
If the shooter's in there, we'll find him.
他就在这
He's in there.
詹尼斯   把你从联邦航空局那得到的资料都转给西恩
Janis, whatever you've got on faa, leave it with to sean.
-你过来下  -等等  这儿还需要她
- Come here. - Wait a minute. I need her here.
我更需要
So do i.
刚在谢克特的办公室里
There was sniper fire at schector's office.
-三个人被狙击手给枪杀了  - 蕾妮不是在那吗?
- We've got three dead bodies. - Where renee was?
-没错  -她还好吧
- Yeah. - Is she okay?
她没事  听着  我需要你给他们提供支援
She's fine. listen, I need you to provide support.
蕾妮认为狙击手就在哥伦比亚大楼里
Renee thinks she has the sniper locked in the columbia building.
特警组在路上  和他们一起把事情搞定
There are swat teams on the way; coordinate with them. okay.
国家安全局想出和那架飞机联系上的方法了吗
Anything else from nsa on how we get through to that plane?
没  据一个和拉森曾经合作过的专家说
No, but we talked to one of the men who worked with latham,
由系统遭受入侵的方式判断
Who said that based on the way the firewall was breeched,
他不认为我们能够成功联系上那架飞机
He doesn't think we can contact.
你好  我是莫斯探员
Yeah, it's agent moss.
怎么样  有什么招吗
Hey, got any help for us?
不要指望国家安全局了  你那边什么情况
Nsa's nowhere. what about you?
我们试图联系飞机上的乘客
We're trying to contact passengers.
但目前为止还不行
So far we haven't been able to get through to anyone.
空军那边的情况如何
What about air force?
他们紧急起飞了一架F16战机进行拦截
They've scrambled an f-16 to intercept,
但离它还差13分钟
But it's still about 13 minutes out.
好  那等会再和你联系
Look, let me get back to you. yeah.
兄弟们  有没有办法破坏他们的通讯
Gus, have you been able to break into their channel yet?
不行  不过我可以清楚地听阿尔梅达和飞行员的谈话
No, but I can hear almeida talking with the pilot.
他指示飞机降落在左31号跑道上
He's landing him on runway three-one-left.
事情不可能这么简单的
It can't be that simple.
他们不会费这么大的劲就仅仅为了
These people didn't take control of this plane
让飞行降落到一条不同的跑道上
Just so they can land it on a different runway.
托德 你的雷达有没有发现进港飞机的异常
Todd, what do you got on your radar that's on approach?
一切正常
Everything looks good.
你的GSA 117怎么样了
And gsa 117?
没有飞行器靠近它
Nothing near it.
这是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is this?!
出什么事了
What happened?
东部区域的所有屏幕都被锁定了
All the screens for the eastern quadrant are locked.
备用系统怎么样了
Try the backup systems.
托德  它们停止工作了
They're not working. todd!
-它被锁定了  -我的也是
- It's locked! - mine, too.
好  现在他们成了瞎子了
Okay, they're blind.
不错
All right...
让东边的那架飞机的飞行航线撞上117航班
Send their sunrise flight into an intersecting landing pattern with 117.
Sri35航班  这是东北三号
Sri35, this is northeast three control.
你被指定了一条新的降落跑道
We have a new runway assignment for you.
请在右4号跑道降落
Runway four-right.
明白  东北三号
Roger that, northeast three.
他正在改变航线
He's changing course.
保罗森
Paulson.
你的屏幕是不是都不动了
How do your screens look over there?
-你是谁  -这无关紧要
-Who is this? -that doesn't matter.
关键是我已经把你的空管权弄到手了
What matters is that I took out your control units.
让CTU赶快追踪这个呼叫
Call the bureau. trace this call.
你究竟想干什么
What the hell do you want?
让你看看我们能够做些什么
I want you to see what we can do.
你不妨打开JFK机场控制塔上的摄像头看看
Why don't you pull up the surveillance cameras at jfk tower.
把JFK机场摄像头给我打开
Give me the cameras at jfk.
糟糕  右四跑道上有一架飞机正在降落
Sid, there's another plane landing on four-right.
它正好穿过左13跑道
It crosses three-one-left.
我的上帝  它们会撞上的
Oh, my god, they're on a collision course.
马上让JFK机场进入紧急状态
Scramble emergency at jfk.
GSA 117  请拉升
Gsa 117, pull up.
紧急情况  马上拉升
Safety alert, pull up.
右四跑道上有飞机降落  立刻拉升
Traffic on runway four-right. pull up.
头  屏幕和通讯都恢复正常了
Sir, we have screens and communication back.
菲力浦  你情况如何
Phil...
一切恢复正常
We're good.
刚才不过是一个警告
That was just a warning shot.
下一次就不再是为了显示我们的能力
Whatever we do next will not be a demonstration.
我们会来真格的
It'll be the real thing.
你们想要什么
What do you people want?
你很快就会知道了
You'll find out soon enough.
爱默生来了
Emerson's here.
把仪器准备好
Get the module ready.
把他的手铐解开
Uncuff him.
那些飞机怎么了
What happened to those planes?
不关你的事
Don't worry about that.
你是不是把它们撞毁了
Did you crash them?
你杀了多少人
How many people did you kill?
把他弄干净
Get him cleaned up.
-你好  托尼  -你好  戴维
- Hey, tony. - david.
计划进行得很顺利
I take it everything went as planned.
是
Yeah.
我们的仪器已经顺利通过测试
The off-site testing the module worked perfectly.
让我看看
Let's see it.
不错
Good.
那就是我们的天才工程师
That's our genius, huh?
是的
Yes, it is.
他看上去有点不听话
Had to be encouraged?
有那么点  不过
Yeah, but...
我已经把他给收拾得服服贴贴
I've got him to a place where he'll do whatever you want.
有空单独聊几句
Can I talk to you a second?
把仪器拿走
Take the module.
告诉我FBI是怎么找到谢克特的
So, tell me how the fbi managed to find schector.
他们利用了我以前的一位同事
They used an old colleague of mine.
我曾经在CTU一起工作的杰克·鲍尔
An agent I worked with at ctu named jack bauer.
我知道他是谁
Yeah, I know who bauer is.
嗯  不过他不是问题
Yeah, well, he's not going to be a problem.
我没让FBI从谢克特嘴里掏出任何东西
I took care of schector before he could tell the fbi anything.
我也会搞定杰克·鲍尔的
I'll take care of jack bauer, too.
我不希望你在新的任务上分心
I don't want you distracted from this new job.
新的任务究竟是什么
Speaking of which, you haven't told me what that is.
坦纳有关于任务的详细情况
Tanner has the specs.
等他到了你自然就明白了
He'll brief you when he gets here.
你为什么现在不告诉我
Why don't you just tell me now?
你现在还不需要知道
'cause you don't need to know yet.
托尼  我们一起合作三年了
Tony, we've been doing this three years.
知道秘密的人越少  大家就越安全
The less information any one of us has, the safer we all are.
振作点  干完这次  我们就洗手不干了
Come on, after this next job, we're done.
把钱赚够  以后就随心所欲了
Cash in our chips, do whatever we want.
那好
All right.
坦纳到了我再联系你
I'll call you when tanner gets here.
好
Okay.
走人
Let's go.
快点  出发
Come on, let's go.
长官  我即将要宣读一份声明
I'm about to make a statement, sir.
有我应该知晓的变化么
Are there any changes I should know about?
不  没有
No, this is fine.
只是要记住  不管他们怎么逼你
Just remember, don't indicate when the go-ahead to invade will be given,
别暗示出下达命令
No matter how hard they push.
但是提及总统在会见前总理马托波
But it's acceptable to mention that the
是可以接受的吧
President is meeting with former prime minister matobo?
是的  而且当他们问及总统是否认为他是朱玛的继任者的时候
Yes. and when they ask whether the president sees him as juma's successor?
没必要隐瞒
No need to hide that fact.
在支持马托波这方面  总统想要最大的曝光
President wants maximum exposure on her support for matobo.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
女士们先生们  早上好
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
尽管全世界进行了谴责  联合国也进行了强制性经济制裁
Despite global condemnation and un-imposed economic sanctions,
本杰明·朱玛将军还是拒绝停止他的种族灭绝
General benjamin juma has refused to stop the genocide that
从他掌管政权以来  他就进行了的野蛮独裁政策
His brutal dictatorship has been perpetrating since he took power.
泰勒总统已经说服世界上很多国家
President taylor has made a persuasive case to the world that
我们将会实施一个全面的军事干预
A full-scale military intervention by us forces and a complete
这也是唯一的方法来彻底推翻朱玛的政权
Overthrow of the juma regime would be the only way to stop the
以此来阻止他继续屠杀无辜的桑加拉的人民
Continued slaughter of the innocent men, women and children of sangala.
好  那边那位
Yes, you there.
安吉拉  总统已经制定了干预的时间表了么
Angela, has the president formulated a time frame for this intervention?
喂
Hello.
长官  航管局刚报告在肯尼迪机场  两架飞机差点相撞
Sir, the faa just reported a near-collision at jfk.
肯尼迪机场
Jfk?
-是的  长官  -多长时间以前
-Yes, sir. -how long ago did this happen?
我可以告诉你  总统现在就在和前总理马托波商谈
I can tell you that president taylor and former prime minister ule
以制定进兵后的策略
Matobo are meeting as we speak to formulate a post-invasion strategy.
我知道你做出了很大的努力
I know how hard you fought to get the
才能为这次军事行动得到支持
Support needed to launch this military operation.
而且我要告诉您  我们的国家会永远感激您
And I want you to know my country will be eternally grateful.
我们的士兵才是你应该感谢的
Our soldiers are the ones truly deserving of your gratitude.
他们才命悬一线的人
They're the people putting their lives on the line.
尽管如此  我了解你冒了很大的政治风险
Still, I know you are taking a great political risk.
我没有保留的余地
I have no reservations.
阻止朱玛是正义的事情
Stopping juma is the right thing to do.
但是当他的政权被推翻的时候
But once he's been removed from power,
得到正当法律的制裁是很关键的
It is critical that he be dealt with in a court of law.
不能让人们留下以暴制暴的印象
And not in a way that would perpetuate the cycle of violence.
朱玛已经杀了我们二十万人民
Juma has killed over 200,000 of our people,
包括我的两个兄弟
Including two of my own brothers.
没人比我更了解以暴制暴的恶性循环了
So no one knows more about the "cycle of violence" Than I do.
但是我的同胞想看到朱玛被惩罚
But my countrymen will want to see juma punished.
那就依法惩处
Then punish him according to the rule of law.
那样你才能在桑加拉推行民主
That's the only way democracy will work in sangala.
如果每个人都依法处置
If no one is treated outside the law.
朱玛也不例外
Not even juma.
我向你保证
You have my word.
现在
And now,
我要去见国防部长
I'd like for us to go over some last-minute
重新看一遍我们的最终行动计划
Operational points with my secretary of defense.
好的
All right.
失陪 马托波先生
Excuse me, mr. matobo.
有什么紧急情况  伊桑
What's the emergency, ethan?
东北航管刚报告说
Northeast air traffic control just reported a
肯尼迪机场两架客机差点相撞
Near-miss between two commercial flights at jfk.
幸运的是  没有人员伤亡
Fortunately, no one was hurt.
认为幕后黑手是阿尔梅达
And we think this man almeida was behind it?
是他
It's him.
我们证实了他的语音印迹
We verified his voice print.
他跟航管通过话  并告诉他们
He contacted air traffic control and told them this
这只是个警告  可以说是大餐前的小开胃菜
Was a demonstration; a shot across the bow, so to speak.
-他要干什么  -他的原话是"你们很快就会知道了"
-What does he want? his exact words were "you'll find out soon enough."
不敢相信
Oh, this is unacceptable.
我的意思是这都是技术问题吗
I mean, it's just technology.
我们应该可以除掉这些混蛋的
We should be able to unplug these bastards.
能想到的我们都试过了  事情没那么简单
Well, we're trying everything we can think of, but it's not that simple.
在找到阿尔梅达上  都做了些什么
What's being done to find almeida?
联调局认为他们跟以前的一个同事关系密切
The fbi believes they're closing in on one of his associates.
他们的时间表是什么
What's their time frame?
还不清楚
That's unclear.
别管那些不重要的空中交通了
Let's go ahead with grounding all nonessential air traffic,
安排一个跟国安局 联调局 国防部的会议
And set up a meeting with homeland, fbi, and dod.
好的  总统女士
Yes, madam president.
说
Yeah.
是谁
Who is it?
等下  是坦纳
Hold on. tanner.
喂  坦纳  发生什么了
Hey, tanner, what's going on?
我被困在哥伦比亚大楼了
I'm trapped in the columbia building.
联调局的人正一层一层的搜查
Fbi's sweeping it right now, floor by floor.
我不知道怎么才能甩掉他们
I don't know how the hell I'll be able to get past them.
我明白
I understand.
你具体在大厦的什么位置
Exactly where in the building are you?
地下室
The basement.
靠近西楼梯井
Near the west stairwell.
我们在12楼
We're on 12th.
收到  第一小组
Roger that, alpha.
第六层检查完毕  我们撤离
Sixth floor's clear. we're moving.
收到  第三小组  去搜查第五层
Copy that. charlie two, moving to the fifth floor.
前进
Proceed.
鲍尔先生
Mr. bauer?
是
Yeah?
我只是想告诉你  在参议院听证会上
I just wanted to tell you-- what they're making
他们那样对待你是不对的
You go through at that senate hearing, it's wrong.
没有啦
No, it's not.
把所有的事情都公布出来更好一些
It's better that everything comes out in the open.
这些年  我们以保护这个国家和人民的名义
We've done so many secret things over the years in the name of
做了许多秘密的事情
Protecting this country ours and the people we promised to protect.
国家和人民有权利知道事实真相
They deserve to know the truth.
那样他们就可以决定  他们想让我们走多远
Then they can decide how far they want to let us go.
尽管这样  那样对你也是不厚道的
Still, you don't deserve to be treated that way,
毕竟你为这个国家做了很多事情
Not after what you've done for our country.
而且不止我一个人这么想
And I'm not the only one who thinks so.
谢谢你
Thank you.
从西楼梯井进入地下室
Entering the basement from the west stairwell.
收到  兰纳德探员
Roger that, agent lennert.
我是来救你出去的
I'm here to get you out.
托尼派我来的
Tony sent me.
怎么出去
How?
把这个穿上
Put this on.
一个特警组小组刚检查过楼梯井
A swat unit just cleared the stairwell.
沿着它上到大厅
Take it up to the lobby.
有辆灰色福特
There's a gray ford parked next to
停在大厦后面空地上的电话亭边
The kiosk in the lot behind the building.
快走
Go.
这里是兰纳德
This is lennert.
-地下室检查完毕  -收到
-Basement level is clear. -roger that.
第一小组在搜查一层  你可以跟他们对接
Alpha team is clearing the first floor. you can hook up with them.
马上
On my way.
沃克 探员  她很厉害是吧
Agent walker, she's good, huh?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
她明白怎样才能把工作做好
She understands what it takes to get the job done.
我可以去车外呼吸点新鲜空气么
You mind if I step out and get some air?
这一大早上都很闷
It's been a hell of a morning.
当然可以
Yeah, sure thing.
别走远  先生
Just stay close, sir.
好
Yeah.
谢谢你
Thanks.
刚从总部得知
Just got an update from headquarters.
你朋友  托尼·阿尔梅达
Your friend, tony almeida,
利用仪器精心策划了一起事件  至使两飞机差点相撞
Just used the device to orchestrate a near-miss between two planes.
他还威胁说下次会玩真的
He's threatening to do it for real next time.
你手下都是统一服装的么
Are all your men represented on the deployment grid?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah. why?
不要轻举妄动  看见走开的那个人了吗
I don't want you to do anything now, but see that man walking away?
他就是狙击手
That's your shooter.
怎么会这样
How can that be possible?
你的人帮他走出了警戒线
If one of your people helped him get through the perimeter.
查一下
Check the grid.
让开
Look out.
没错  他不是我们的人
You're right. he's not one of ours.
我们跟踪他  看看能不能带我们找到托尼·阿尔梅达
We'll follow him, see if he leads us back to almeida-- dornan.
不  这样做不对
No, that's not the right move.
不知道局里做了多少让步之前
You can't bring anyone else into this,
不能让其他人牵扯进来
Not until you know how badly the bureau's been compromised.
好  那你说怎么做
Okay, so what are you suggesting?
我们自己来
We can do this on our own.
沃克探员
Yes, agent walker?
长官
Ma'am?
在大楼东边安排更多警力
Put more agents on the eastern edge of the building.
看上去警力不足
The perimeter looks light.
好的
On it.
-做得对  -走着瞧
You made the right call. we'll see.
我要用你的车
I need your vehicle.
现在插播一条新闻
We have some breaking news to tell you about right now.
经联邦航空局确认  不久前在肯尼迪机场
The faa confirms a near-miss between two planes
两架航班险些相撞
At jfk international airport just a short time ago.
因此所有即将离港航班将停留待命
As a result, outgoing flights nationwide are now grounded.
已经升空的飞机将在下个航点停靠
Planes already in the air will be grounded once they land.
听着  拉森
The faa... listen to me, latham.
照之前说得做  才能保命
Do as you're told, you'll stay alive.
明白吗
You understand?
把他关到储藏室去  看住了
Put him in storage. watch him.
杜巴库先生  这个威胁很不错吧
an effective demonstration, wouldn't you say, mr. dubaku?
非常有效
Very effective.
朱玛上校会对此很满意的
General juma will be pleased.
就是那个仪器吗
Is that the module?
按要求设计的
As promised.
为了以防万一  我把设计者也带来了
And I've brought the man who constructed it
以便在有必要的情况下进行修正
Here in case there are any modifications necessary.
如此一来  足以向白宫方面证实我们的实力了  杜巴库先生
Well, now that we've impressed upon the white house what we can do, mr.Dubaku
或许该是时候让泰勒总统知道
Perhaps now would be a good time to
你们需要的是什么东西了
Make your demands known to president taylor.
准备一下
Make the preparations.
你们的政府不仅杀了我哥哥  还想来杀我
Your government killed my brother and they tried to kill me.
现在他们将付出巨额的罚金
Now they are going to pay a very steep price for...
涉足我们的私事
...interfering in our affairs.
联邦航空局正在降落航班  目前为止平安无事
Faa is landing flights, so far without incident,
不过照之前他们的行事习惯  在任何时候都有可能
But these people have proven what they can do, and at any time,
破坏空中交通或者
Can sabotage air traffic or any of the
我们现有的基础设施  已经越过了防火墙
Infrastructure systems we have beyond the firewall.
在修复工作上  国家安全局有时间计划吗
Does nsa have a timeframe on fixing it
这样才是长久之计
So we can keep these people out permanently?
总统夫人  CIP是多年积累的工程项目
Madame president, the cip firewall was the result of a multi-year project.
重新设计代码需要几周甚至几月的时间
Reengineering the code could take weeks or months.
也就是说  国家安全局也不清楚
At this point, nsa just doesn't know.
确切点说哪类体系易受攻击  科尔内先生
Exactly what systems are vulnerable, dr. cornell?
首当其冲的应是国家电网
At the top of the list would be the national power grid.
一旦瘫痪
If disabled,
将不可能为数百万人的供应电力
We could end up being unable to deliver power to many millions of people.
大规模的灯火管制将
A blackout of that scale would almost
导致大城市的骚乱
Certainly result in rioting in the major cities.
比之更为严重的是水处理和传输系统
Even more critical are the water treatment and distribution systems.
通过破坏关键的大坝和污水处理厂
By sabotaging key dams and sewage processing plants,
甚至大规模的污染饮用水
They could contaminate drinking water on a massive scale.
由此而导致的中毒致死将是空前绝后的
Deaths from poisoning would be substantial up front and massive
随之而来的
Casualties would follow soon thereafter
将是更多的人由于脱水而致死
As people began to die from dehydration.
有办法保护这些系统吗
Is there any way to protect these systems?
唯一的办法就是在短时间内将其关闭
The only way would be shutting them down, and then, within a short time,
如此一来  不能给人们提供
It would be impossible to supply the
充足的事物和干净的水
Population with sufficient food and clean water.
这样做的结果就是加剧了社会的动荡局面
The resulting civil unrest would undoubtedly aggravate the situation.
这是最新的预测报告
Here are the latest projections.
谢谢
Thank you.
伊桑·卡宁
Ethan kanin.
卡宁先生
Mr. kanin
我跟第一先生在一起
I'm with the first gentleman.
你和他在哪里
With him where?
他在干什么
What's he doing?
泰勒先生正在去见他前任女友罗杰的路上
Mr. taylor is on his way to confront roger's former girlfriend.
我还以为他放弃了
I thought he gave up on all of this.
长官  儿子被谋杀这事儿已经把他消耗殆尽了
Sir, he's consumed by the idea that his son was murdered,
在过去的两个月里
And for the past two months,
他一直在以私人名义雇用侦探
He's been pursuing that belief through a private
调查这件事
Detective he hired without the president's knowledge.
上帝啊
My god.
为什么我刚刚才知道这件事
Why is this the first time I'm hearing anything about this?
我为此负责  长官
I take full responsibility for that, sir.
泰勒先生用我来保证他的活动远离官方途径
Mr. Taylor enlisted me in keeping his activities off the official manifest,
不过   情况有点失控
But, uh, it's gotten out of hand.
就这点来说  我很担心泰勒先生的
And at this point, I'm worried about mr. taylor's...
心态
State of mind.
我认为总统有必要知道这边发生了什么
I think the president needs to know what's going on.
好吧
All right.
谢谢你   盖齐探员
Thank you, agent gedge.
盖齐探员
Agent gedge?
在  先生
Sir?
没什么问题吧
Everything all right?
是的先生  办个手续而已
Yes, sir. just checking in.
灾难前的准备工作还不够妥当
Building disaster preparedness scenarios is not enough.
我希望负责人能把
I want the governors to put the
国民警卫队安排在预先部署的地方
National guard on a pre-deployment footing.
直到我们找出幕后黑手
And until we find and stop the people behind this,
我觉得有必要提升警报等级
I think we should talk about raising the alert level.
是的  长官  我们已经把那栋建筑戒严了
Yes, sir, we have the building locked down,
同时我们正在搜捕之前提到的嫌犯
And we're searching for the suspect as we speak.
这已经是最高优先级了  长官
It's our highest priority, sir.
明白  长官
Understood, sir.
白宫上下都在关注这个
The white house is all over this.
国土安全局更依赖我们
Homeland's leaning on us.
我们现在去找那家伙
We have got to find this guy now.
多曼的小队已经完成了对大楼的第一轮搜捕
Dornan's team is almost done with their first sweep through the building,
但他说凭直觉那狙击手根本不在那里
But he said it's his gut feeling that the sniper is not in there.
我可不管他什么直觉
I don't care about his gut feeling.
蕾妮说他们在
Renee said they had that building
枪响之后就立刻对大楼进行了戒严
Locked down right after the shots were fired.
他肯定在那里
He's got to be in there.
-遵命  长官  -让他们不要放过任何角落
Yes, sir. tell them to search every square inch.
-呃...  -还有什么事
Uh, uh, uh... what?
多曼也想知道我们有没有沃克探员的下落
Dornan also wants to know if we know where agent walker is.
她不在那里吗
She's not at the scene?
十分钟前她没登记就走了
She left ten minutes ago without logging her destination.
鲍尔呢
What about bauer?
他也一起走了
He left the scene with her.
前面堵车了
He's coming up on heavy traffic.
你可以开慢点
You can drop back a little more.
没关系  我看着他呢
It's all right. I've got him.
是拉里
It's larry.
别接
Don't answer it.
那他就会起疑心的
Then he'll get worried or suspicious.
喂
Hey.
多曼说你离开现场了
Dornan said you left the scene.
为什么  发生什么事了
Why? what's going on?
反恐特警组将一切控制得很好
Swat has the operation well in hand.
我在查别的线索
I'm following up on a lead.
-什么线索  -在谢克特住处找到的武器
What lead? a weapon we found at schector's.
有一部分枪支编号
There's a partial serial number.
我想通过它查到卖家
I want to run it past a source.
你和鲍尔在一起吗
With bauer?
是的  他和我在一起
Uh, yes, he's accompanying me.
蕾妮
Renee...
到底怎么回事儿
What the hell's going on?
你指什么
What are you talking about?
眼下只有通过查清那个枪手的情况
Getting our hands on that shooter is our best
才能找到阿尔梅达和那个装置
Chance of finding Almeida and finding that device.
你不能轻易因为其他探员提供的线索
And I don't think you'd turn your back on that operation
而背离整个既定行动
For a lead you could easily have passed off to another agent.
我不确定你是什么意思
I'm not sure what you're getting at.
我也是
Neither am i.
鲍尔让你参与到什么行动里了吗
Has bauer gotten you involved with something?
拉里  你相信我吗
Larry, do you trust me?
你我心照不宣
You know the answer to that.
那请相信我
Then please just accept what I'm telling you.
我们正在追查一条线索
We're following up on a lead,
一有发现  我第一时间向你汇报
And I will fill you in if and when we find something.
好的
All right.
该死
Damn it.
我不喜欢这样
I do not like this.
我厌倦了欺骗我的上司
I just flat out lied to my boss.
他信了吗
Did he buy it?
我们没事儿了吧
Are we in the clear?
我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
好  谢谢
Good. thanks.
蕾妮的通信器联线了吗
Is Renee's comm unit active?
是的  她开着对讲机
Yeah. her walkie's on.
能定位吗
Can you do a triangulation on it?
系统可不允许这么做
Well, that's not really what the system is set up for.
-但  我试试看  -认真点
But I can try. do more than try.
我要知道她的位置
I want to know where she is.
-你打电话不就行了  -珍妮丝...
Can you not just call her? Janis...
做就是了
Just do it.
好吧
Okay.
在谢克特办公室时
Back at schector's office,
我要你让他说出阿尔梅达的位置
When I told you to get Almeida's location out of him,
你准备下多重的手
How far were you planning to go with that?
是你要我不惜一切代价的
You told me to do whatever it takes.
对  我是说让你吓一下他
Yeah, I said that for schector's benefit, to scare him,
但你当时真准备下狠手
But you were actually planning to do it.
你会怎么对他
How far would you have gone?
这已不重要了
It doesn't matter now.
在我看很重要
It does to me.
因为你我押上了我的前程
I just put my career on the line because of you,
我只想知道我在和谁打交道
And I'd like to know who I'm dealing with.
你看过我的资料了
Yeah, well, you read my file.
资料上看不出你刚才的行事准则
Your file doesn't tell me how you justify the things that you've done.
最近我不断在为我的所作所为做回答
You know, I've been answering a lot of questions lately about my past and,
老实说  我烦透了
Frankly, I'm done.
我告诉你帮你找到托尼·阿尔梅达
I told you I'd help you find Tony Almeida.
我甚至答应照你的做
I even agreed to do it your way.
既然FBI已不可靠  我们别无选择
Since the fbi's been compromised, that's no longer an option.
我现在还能帮你找到他
Now, I can still help you find him,
但你要让我按我的方法来做
But you're going to have to let me do it my way.
没问题吧
Is that going to be a problem?
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
我知道你认为这么做不对
I know you think this is a mistake.
先生  我无权评论
It's not my place to say that, sir.
就算是又怎样
And if it was?
先生  当局已经对你儿子女友进行询问了
The authorities have already questioned your son's girlfriend, sir.
我不是说这个
Not about this.
他们认为我儿子是自杀
They assumed my son killed himself and
因此对他的案子草草了之
Didn't look deeply enough into anything.
这边走  先生
This way, sir.
尽管市场目前疲软
Well, even though the market's been soft,
但您一定不愿错过这项投资
You don't want to hedge your buy on this.
我今天只能买那么多了
It's really all I can do today.
要知道一万股可太少了
You know 10,000 shares isn't going to cut it.
稍等一下
Excuse me a moment.
萨曼莎·罗斯
Samantha roth.
罗斯小姐  有特工要见您
Miss roth, there is a secret service agent here to see you.
什么
What?
他在前台
He's at reception.
要找人把他带去你哪里吗
Would you like me to have someone show him to your desk?
不用了  我过来
No. um, I'll be right there.
好的
All right.
我回头给您电话
Let me call you back.
好的
Sure.
女士
Ma'am.
泰勒先生
Mr. taylor?
真意外啊
This is quite a surprise.
您好吗
How are you?
萨曼莎  我想私下和你聊聊
I wanted to have a word with you, sam, in private.
当然可以
Of course.
很抱歉  罗杰葬礼后咱俩都没联系过
I'm-i'm really sorry we haven't spoken since roger's funeral.
我  我一直很难过
It's just... it's been so difficult for me.
萨曼  钱的事儿我知道了
I know about the money, sam.
您说什么
Excuse me?
40万美元被转账到开曼群岛的海外帐户上
$400,000 wired to an offshore account in the cayman Islands
恰巧就在你发现我儿子尸体的三天后
three days after you found my son's body.
别狡辩了
There's no point in denying it.
-我只想知道是谁  为什么给你钱  -给我钱?
I just want to know who paid you and why. paid me?
你知道我儿子真正的死因
You know something about my son's death,
有人花钱让你闭嘴
And somebody's paid you to keep quiet about it.
泰勒先生  事情不是这样的
Mr. taylor, that is just not true.
请你回答我的问题
Please, just answer the question!
钱
The money...
钱  不是我的
It... it isn't mine.
什么意思
What do you mean, it's not yours?
那是我伯母的钱
It belongs to my aunt.
去年我伯父过世后  她生活很拮据
She's had financial difficulties since my uncle passed away last year.
那是伯父留下的房产
It's from his divested real estate holdings.
我让她把钱转到海外帐户  逃避国税局查账
I suggested she move it to an offshore account to hide it from the irs.
你要我相信  我儿子死后三天  你却能镇定地
You want me to believe you had the presence of mind to commit
操作一起税务欺诈  他可是你的爱人
Tax fraud three days after my son died, the man you supposedly loved?
我爱过他
I did love him.
我说的也是实话
And I'm telling you the truth.
你要相信我
You have to believe me.
我不信
I don't.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
要是你固执己见  我俩也无话可说
Well, if that's what you think then we have nothing left to talk about...
告诉我事实  否则你别想走
You're not going anywhere till I get the truth.
放手
Let go of me.
先生
Sir!
你知道凶手
You know who murdered my son.
没人杀了他
No one murdered him.
他是自杀的
He killed himself.
泰勒先生  我们该走了  现在
Mr. taylor, we need to go. right now.
我会找出事实真相的  到时候你就祈祷上帝吧
I'm going to find out what you're hiding, and when I do, god help you.
坦纳
Tanner.
我出来了
I'm out.
收到   Emerson和局里的内线联系上了
Copy that. emerson spoke to his man inside the bureau.
-他说你没事了  -好的
He says you're clear. good.
我要为下一步行动安排人手
I need to prep my men on the next job
你告诉我们该做什么
So why don't you tell me what we need.
规格等我到了再告诉你
I'll give you the specs when I get there.
你到哪了
Where are you?
我正要开进来了
I'm just pulling in right now.
我们做好准备
We'll be standing by.
坦纳一到我们就离开
When tanner gets here, we'll take off.
大家收拾一下  你执行删除程序
Why don't you start the deletion program while we pack up?
该死  不能再走了
Damn it. we can't go any farther.
他会发现我们的  抓稳了
He'll make us. hold on.
沃克探员  我们得走了
Agent walker, we need to go!
给  你会用得上
Here. you're going to need this.
谢谢
Thank you.
我和他交火  掩护我侧翼
I'll engage him. cover my flank.
我能行
I can handle it.
好  走吧
Okay, let's go.
快
Now.
放下武器
Put the weapon down.
快
Now!
托尼·阿尔梅达在船上吗
Is tony almeida on the boat?
不知道
I don't know.
杰克
Jack!
没关系
It doesn't matter.
阿尔梅达不是首要目标  那仪器才是
Almeida's not the priority. the device is.
我们得马上进去
We have to go in now.
监视录像失灵
Surveillance camera went out.
去看一下
Go check it out.
掩护我
Cover me.
可恶
Damn it!
托尼
Tony!
别动
Stop!
可恶
Damn it.
仪器不见了
The device is gone.
定位器记录已经被删除了
The locator files have been deleted.
在哪里
Where is it?!
好
Okay.
你这是怎么了
What happened to you?
你到底是怎么了
What the hell happened to you?